[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of color is the shade called saffron?", "correct_answer": "Yellow", "incorrect_answers": ["Green", "Red", "Blue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Blackjack, it is crucial for the player not to let neither the dealer nor the other players see his/her cards.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these countries is the oldest independent constitutional republic?", "correct_answer": "San Marino", "incorrect_answers": ["Iceland", "Monaco", "Costa Rica"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following powers does Hancock, from the self-titled movie, not have?", "correct_answer": "X-Ray vision", "incorrect_answers": ["Super sharp nails", "None of the Above", "Super Strength"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Midnight Run, Jack Walsh is having trouble taking Jonathan Mardukas back to Los Angeles right away. Why is he having trouble taking him back?", "correct_answer": "Mardukas is afraid of flying", "incorrect_answers": ["Jack Walsh forgot his wallet and has no money to buy  airline tickets", "Mardukas does not have identification to get on the plane", "They miss their flight and are unable to get another one"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the national motto of India, Satyameva Jayate, mean in Sanskrit?", "correct_answer": "Truth Alone Triumphs", "incorrect_answers": ["The Supreme Treasure of Truth", "Truth Is The Best Way", "Truth Is Divine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The call of the Blue Jay is often compared to the sound produced by this object.", "correct_answer": "Rusty pump", "incorrect_answers": ["Screeching door", "Flute", "Old trombone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the green color associated with during the Middle Ages according to some stories from that period?", "correct_answer": "Lust", "incorrect_answers": ["Friendship", "Rivalry", "Royalty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first couple to be shown in bed together on prime time television was this.", "correct_answer": "Johnny and Mary Kay Stearns", "incorrect_answers": ["The Simpsons", "The Jetsons", "The Adams"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was named by the United Nations as the Year of the Dolphin?", "correct_answer": "2007", "incorrect_answers": ["1985", "2000", "1999"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do the children do with their obese mothers dead body in the 1993 drama movie Whats Eating Gilbert Grape?", "correct_answer": "Burn it along with the house", "incorrect_answers": ["Lift it with a helicopter", "Desert it", "Bury it in the back yard"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A panther and a black leopard are the same animal.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]